<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Majurin muistelmat</title>
		<description>Iuwenis in Aeternum</description>
		<link>/</link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Jäynä Quiz for the Jäynä Finale!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Jäynä sent me this quiz - test your knowledge of famous Jäynäs of the past, and come today at 16 to the Jäynä Finale to see more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; style=&quot;height:100vh&quot; src=&quot;https://awesome-bose-a9b2a2.netlify.app/&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/04/22/J%C3%A4yn%C3%A4visa-finaalin-ratoksi.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/04/22/J%C3%A4yn%C3%A4visa-finaalin-ratoksi.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>2nd Commandment</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2nd.commandment.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2nd Commandment&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/2nd.commandment.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;btn btn-outline-dark&quot;&gt;Open&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/04/13/2.-paivakasky.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/04/13/2.-paivakasky.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quarantine, Day 15</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is the disappointment of all disappointments. The situation caused by the Corona virus has already been going on for two weeks. Wappu is coming and the new white Teekkari Caps for the Freshmen will soon be here. It is time to roll up our sleeves and crack down, as nothing in this world can stop the birth of the new Teekkari generation! Freshmen must get their caps by hook or by crook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/03/27/Karanteeni_paiva_15.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/03/27/Karanteeni_paiva_15.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quarantine, Day 1</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Even the oldest Teekkari of them all wouldn’t believe what is happening around the world. Some insidious virus began to spread from China and has now reached Finland and even our beloved Otaniemi. Events have been cancelled and the near future seems very unclear. However, the Freshmen Committee has not let this discourage them. The Committee will relentlessly continue on its mission to carry out the important work of educating the generation of Teekkari Freshmen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/03/13/Karanteeni_paiva_1.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/03/13/Karanteeni_paiva_1.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Spring planning</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The spring is closing in fast, and planning has taken plenty of time. Our committee has put countless hours into planning the spring, and it certainly takes its toll on everyone. However, the spirits are high among the committee, and I am impatiently waiting with them to get to arrange everything!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/03/10/Kevaan_suunnittelua.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/03/10/Kevaan_suunnittelua.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Orienteering badges</title>
				<description>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img style=&quot;width:80%&quot; src=&quot;/assets/suunnistusmerkit.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic! Now all of the orienteering adventures have been held and boy was it fun. I sewed the badges to my overalls and don’t they look nice all in a row together? Now my overalls are ready for the spring!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/02/20/Suunnistusmerkit.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/02/20/Suunnistusmerkit.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Spring's annual ball</title>
				<description>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img style=&quot;width:80%&quot; src=&quot;/assets/vujukuva.JPG&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was wonderful to represent the freshmen committee in Potentiaalin Tasaus. SIK turned 99 and the ball was fancier than ever. We got to dine and enjoy the main event in Vanha Poli at Bulevardi which is the the old home of technical university. The ball was great and we got to see some old friends in the annual ball committee as well. We had a blast and off we went to sillis in the the next morning. SIK turns 100 this year and the starting blast of the year started at sillis. Got to go home with a belly full of food.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/02/15/Kevaan_vuosijuhlakasa.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/02/15/Kevaan_vuosijuhlakasa.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Winterday</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;A cold flake of snow flew into my face yet it did not disturb the sea of asphalt that rose and fell so beautifully in Otaniemi, Teekkarikylä and Otakaari. We had saunas to make sure that they were working correctly. I just needed to remember to inform the IE-director of this. Brave freshmen marched the lands and fields, performing tricks, dances, jumps in order to receive credit where credit was due. New winds started to blow and peace crawled up to the Major’s heart. It’s time for the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fabulous festivities started off in high spirits and I couldn’t hear the Freshmen Captains over the booming of the dance floor! Even the new guards got changed into their vests and were ready for action.The night grew darker and louder, the party was just getting started. The performer was a success and of course the company was fantastic. It was really an honor to watch the freshmen reach for the skies. I wonder, I feel a little breeze of spring in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2020/01/14/Talvipaiva.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2020/01/14/Talvipaiva.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Freshman committee’s recreation</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;It was very nice to see my own committee again! A lot of work had been done over the autumn and it was finally time for our recreation days with the whole Freshman Committee. Overcooked and Disney-monopoly was great fun with the Captains!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week we also had FTMK’s pre Christmas party. We made food together and enjoyed the warmth of the sauna. It was nice to see how the committee keeps going and has been keeping spirits high despite the tiring and intense autumn.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2019/11/30/Fuksitoimikunnan_virkistykset.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2019/11/30/Fuksitoimikunnan_virkistykset.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>International Bachelor of Science Annual Freshmen Sitsit</title>
				<description>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img style=&quot;width:80%&quot; src=&quot;/assets/enkkusitsit.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The upstairs of OK20 was transformed into a stylish and atmospheric venue for the first ever annual sitsit for the Freshmen of the new Bachelor of Science degree programmes. It was heartwarming to see so many of the new Freshmen coming together and taking part in the sitsit culture with such enthusiasm and joy. The head work of the International Bachelor Freshmen Captains had paid off and the sitsit brought song and cheer into everyone’s hearts and into the ever colder and ever longer autumn nights. It was great to be able to welcome so many new students from around the world into the Teekari culture and see their enjoyment and enthusiasm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<link>/2019/11/18/International_Bachelor_of_Science-Annual_Freshmen_Sitsit.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/2019/11/18/International_Bachelor_of_Science-Annual_Freshmen_Sitsit.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
